<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <title>Little Seeds</title>
  <release-date>15 June, 2017</release-date>
  <website>https://noemieszm.itch.io/littleseeds</website>

  <platforms>
    <platform>
      <name>HTC Vive on Windows</name>
      <link>https://noemieszm.itch.io/littleseeds</link>
    </platform>
  </platforms>

 <price>
  <currency></currency>
  <value>Free</value>
</price>

  <description>
    Little Seeds is a short relaxing VR experience
  </description>

  <histories>
    <history>
      <header>My work</header>
       <text>
       It was my first VR game, my first 3D game and my first Unreal Engine game. I worked more specifically on trees :
       one of the challenge of the game was to make trees grow in real time. I used the fresh new UE Procedural Mesh library
       to achieve this. I also worked on the game controls, wich differ from an usual VR game. And I also learned how 
       to optimize a game, since VR is very expensive.
       Beside my work as a programer, I also organized the last sprint of the project.
       </text>
    </history>
    <history>
      <header>The project</header>
      <text>
        Little Seeds is a three month student project made at CNAM-ENJMIN. We were a team of seven people :
        a manager, a game designer, a graphic artist, a UX designer, a sound designer and two programmer.
        It was our first "real" game project. 
      </text>
    </history>
    <history>
      <header>The game</header>
       <text>
       Little Seeds is a relaxing VR game, wich take place in a dreamed garden. With simple controls,
       he can pick a seed, put it into a put, water it to make a tree grow, prune it, and then plant 
       it in the garden. He can also teleport in different place in the garden, enjoying the river or
       the birds flying.
       From the beginning we wanted to make this game for everyone, even people who doesn't play video game.
       </text>
    </history>
  </histories>

  <features>
    <feature>Unreal Engine 4</feature>
    <feature>Blueprints and C++</feature>
    <feature>Sound integration using Wwise</feature>
    <feature>Live growing trees, using Procedural Meshes</feature>
    <feature>Graphic optimization</feature>
    <feature>VR usability</feature>
    <feature>Some team management</feature>
  </features>

  <trailers>
    <trailer>
      <name>Teaser</name>
      <youtube>
        FgQw1B4FfPc
      </youtube>
    </trailer>
    <trailer>
      <name>Walkthrough</name>
      <youtube>
        mFEax7faLuk
      </youtube>
    </trailer>
  </trailers>

  <!-- You can set your widgets here (optional): -->
  <widgets>
    <itch>
      151452
    </itch>
  </widgets>

</product> 
